Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
1953-1963
YCAL MSS 266
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
188.49
(453 boxes)
The Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts contains approximately five thousand American television scripts dating from about 1953 to 1963. The scripts offer insight into programming during the period in which television became a fixture in the average home and the primary medium for news and entertainment. The collection contains a wide range of program genres, including variety shows, drama serials, historical drama, crime drama and reenactments, plays, situation comedies, westerns, documentaries, interviews, music, and religious programs. All three major broadcast networks in the United States during this time period--ABC, CBS, and NBC--are represented. The collection also contains a small number of press releases and some material documenting the activities of TV Key, including draft reports and synopses.
Scheuer, Steven H., 1926-2014
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Steven H. Scheuer, 1964.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Steven H. Scheuer (1926-)
Steven H. Scheuer is a television and film critic. His syndicated preview column "TV Key" ran in newspapers throughout the United States beginning in 1953, and he edited the related annual publication TV Key Movie Guide, later Movies on TV.
Scope and Contents
The Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts contains approximately five thousand American television scripts dating from about 1953 to 1963. The scripts offer insight into programming during the period in which television became a fixture in the average home and the primary medium for news and entertainment. The collection contains a wide range of program genres, including variety shows, drama serials, historical drama, crime drama and reenactments, plays, situation comedies, westerns, documentaries, interviews, music, and religious programs. All three major broadcast networks in the United States during this time period--ABC, CBS, and NBC--are represented. The collection also contains a small number of press releases and some material documenting the activities of TV Key, including draft reports and synopses.
An index of authors, subjects, and interview subjects can be found in Appendices I-III, at the end of the finding aid.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by program title. Following the main alphabetic sequence, under the heading "Specials," are scripts and fragments not identifiable as part of a program series. One box of TV Key press releases is filed at the end of the collection. Folders numbers begin again with number 1 in each box.
Appendix I: Alphabetical Index of Authors
Author listings are followed by box and folder numbers and name of program. For example: "Abbott, George 318:4 Pond's Theatre" is a reference to a script by George Abbott stored in box 318, folder 4, filed with other scripts in the "Pond's Theatre" series.
Names of programs are not repeated for subsequent entries under the same author.
Abbott, George 318:4 Pond's Theater
34:7 Best of Broadway
Abelow, S.I. 2:8 Alcoa Hour
Abernethy, Robert 447:4 Documentary Special
Ace, Goodman 35 The Big Party
173 Kraft Music Hall
290 The Perry Como Show
296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
318 Pontiac Star Parade
Adamson, Ed 83:6 Danger
Adelman, Jerry 438:11 Drama Special
Adler, Marjorie 263:11 NBC Matinee Theater
271:2
274:9
Agee, James 282:4 Omnibus
Aiken, Conrad 351:2 Studio One
363:8
Aldrich, David 364:9 Studio One
Alexander, Alton 147 Hollywood Screen Test
Alexander, Ronald 380 Too Young to go Steady
Aley, Albert 380 Treasury Men in Action
Alkon, Selig 194 Let's Take a Trip
Allan, Andrew 99:4 Front Row Center
Allardice, James 122 George Gobel Show
214:5 Lux Video Theater
214:7
Allen, Dave 11:2 Armstrong Circle Theater
Allen, Fred 280:14 Omnibus
Allen, Ray 335 Saturday Color Carnival
Allen, Steve 81:5 Danger
434 Entertainment Special
Allen, Woody 106 The Garry Moore Show
286 Pat Boone Chevy Showroom
435:4 Entertainment Special
Allensworth, Carl 183:2 Kraft Television Theater
Alsburg, Arthur 240 My Favorite Husband
283 Our Miss Brooks
Altman, William M. 359:2 Studio One
363:7
377:2
Anderson, Robert 226:17 Medallion Theater
351:5 Studio One
373:11
Anderson, Maxwell 439:2 Drama Special
Andrews, Lillian 103 Frontiers of Faith
Angelos, Bill 296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
Anton, Don Rozi 178:2 Kraft Television Theater
Appell, Don 89:1 Dumont Television Network
Apstein, Theodore 82:14 Danger
83:1
121:8 General Electric Theater
146:4 Hallmark Hall of Fame
252:1 NBC Matinee Theater
257:3
257:6
262:5
264:8
265:10
267:4
269:11
271:12
273:1
273:10
275:1
367:8 Studio One
393:1 United States Steel Hour
393:3
439:8 Drama Special
440:6
Ardrey, Robert 317:8 Pond's Theater
Arent, Arthur 224:3 Maurice Evans Presents
262:10 NBC Matinee Theater
382:5 United States Steel Hour
383:1
385:1
387:6
389:4
Arnold, Buddy 415 Washington Square
Arnothy, Christine 192:8 Kraft Television Theater
Arthur, Kay 9:4 Armstrong Circle Theater
245:6
246:3
254:4
258:2
340:13 Star Stage
342:13 Star Tonight
386:3 United States Steel Hour
390:5
399:2
400:4
402:5
Arthur, Robert Alan: see Aurthur, Robert Alan.
Asinof, Eliot 71:1 Climax!
92 Ellery Queen
133:2 Goodyear Playhouse
Atkins, Violet 432:2 You Are There
432:6
432:13
Atkinson, B.M. 252:6 NBC Matinee Theater
255:6
Aurelio, Richard 196 Lamp Unto My Feet
Aurthur, Robert Alan 11:4 Armstrong Circle Theater
28:5
45 Bonino
58:9 Campbell Soundstage
130:7 Goodyear Television Playhouse
131:7
138:11 Gulf Playhouse
154 Jamie
166 Justice
308:13 Philco Television Playhouse
309:2
310:10
312:8
314:4
319:3 Producer's Showcase
366:1 Studio One
408:2 United States Steel Hour
Avery, Ira 129:1 Goodyear Television Playhouse
310:3 Philco Television Playhouse
392:5 United States Steel Hour
Avery, Jane 392:5 United States Steel Hour
Axelrod, George 354:3 Studio One
Aylesworth, John 173 Kraft Music Hall
295 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
Azine, Harold 421 Wide Wide World
Babson, Naomi Lane 254:2 NBC Matinee Theater
Baehr, Nicholas 9:8 Armstrong Circle Theater
10:15
90:2 DuPont Show of the Week
104 Further Adventures of Ellery Queen
148 The Investigator
193:2 Kraft Television Theater
249:6 NBC Matinee Theater
252:4
254:11
258:7
264:1
265:1
268:3
271:8
282:4 Omnibus
341:10 Star Tonight
341:14
413:3 United States Steel Hour
Baer, Art 296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
Baer, Dick 233 The Mighty O
321 Professional Father
Bagni, Gwen 75:2 Climax!
76:6
77:1
Bailey, Anne Howard 6:9 Appointment With Adventure
7:1
7:13
8:6
10:11 Armstrong Circle Theater
11:8
13:1
165:8 Johnson's Wax Theater
168:6 Justice
168:7
168:8
169:5
209:13 Lux Video Theater
210:2
210:3
211:1
342:2 Star Tonight
Bailey, Ray 161:6 Johnson's Wax Theater
Bailey, Mel 442:10 Documentary Special
446:2
Baker, Dorothy 197 Life With Father
Baker, Elliott 22:7 Armstrong Circle Theater
23:4
103 Frontiers of Faith
451:3 General Motors Presents
138 Great Ghost Tales
162:7 Johnson's Wax Theater
398:1 United States Steel Hour
445:7 Documentary Special
Baker, George 8:4 Appointment With Adventure
Baker, Herbert 296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
338 Shower of Stars
Baker, Marion C. 256:1 NBC Matinee Theater
(Baldwin, Faith) 375:10 Suspense Theater
(Balzac, Honorede) 275:5 NBC Matinee Theater
Banks, Frances 276:3 NBC Matinee Theater
Barasch, Norman 106 Garry Moore Show
308:10 The Peter Lind Hayes Show
378:14 The Teresa Brewer Show
(Barker, Granville) 360:6 Studio One
Barnett, Sanford 211:3 Lux Video Theater
211:5
211:6
211:7
212:1
212:2
212:3
212:4
213:1
213:5
214:4
214:6
214:9
215:1
215:6
215:8
216:1
216:4
216:6
217:1
218:7
219:1
219:4
220:1
220:4
221:3
222:7
Barnouw, Erick 382:1 United States Steel Hour
382:3
404:3
404:4
Barrett, Bill 5:5 Alcoa Hour
Barrett, James Lee 190:2 Kraft Television Theater
193:6
195:4
Barron, Arthur 421 White Paper
Barry, Joe 263:1 NBC Matinee Theater
Barry, Peter 247:7 NBC Matinee Theater
261:8
360:3 Studio One
Barry, Philip 34:4 Best of Broadway
237:8 Motorola TV Hour
253:1 NBC Matinee Theater
Barton, Franklin 171:7 Kaiser Aluminum Hour
260:5 NBC Matinee Theater
336:4 Schick Theater
Barton, Pat 278 Odyssey
Baumer, Maria 81:6 Danger
Beauchamp, D.D. 200 The Lineup
Beaumont, Don 122 George Gobel
259:6 NBC Matinee Theater
Becker, Lester 88 Directions
103 Frontiers of Faith
Behrstock, Arthur 340:6 Star Stage
Belkin, Gary 46 Caesar's Hour
Bell, Mary Hayley 157:6 Johnson's Wax Theater
Bellah, James Warner 121:1 General Electric Theater
441:6 Drama Special
Bellak, George 11:3 Armstrong Circle Theater
84:3 Danger
84:14
85:2
85:3
85:6
121:1 General Electric Theater
154 Jamie
167:6 Justice
168:1
168:4
227:5 Medallion Theater
270:23 NBC Matinee Theater
279:10 Omnibus
340:11 Star Stage
340:17
359:6 Studio One
363:3
376:3 Suspense Theater
394:5 United States Steel Hour
438:9 Drama Special
Bellen, Robert Leslie 97:11 Eye-Witness
Benet, Stephen Vincent 1:3 ABC Album
121:18 General Electric Theater
439:7 Drama Special
Benjamin, Burton 163:2 Johnson's Wax Theater
163:4
188:1 Kraft Television Theater
Benjamin, James 163:2
188:1 Kraft Television Theater
233:4 Mennen Hour
379:10 Thresholds For Tomorrow
442:3 Documentary Special
442:5
Benjamin, John 278 Odyssey
Bennet, Charles 212:6 Lux Video Theater
213:4
Bennet, Margot 173:9 Kraft Mystery Theater
Bennet, Jack 431:14 You Are There
432:4
432:8
432:10
432:12
433:4
433:6
433:10
Benoff, Mac 415 Washington Square
Benz, Hamilton 9:6 Armstrong Circle Theater
9:14
58:10 Campbell Soundstage
441:4 Drama Special
Bercovitch, Reuben 218:2 Lux Video Theater
Berg, Dick 172:3 Kaiser Aluminum Hour
184:7 Kraft Television Theater
233:1 Mennen Hour
363:4 Studio One
Berg, Gertrude 91:2 Elgin Hour
127 The Goldbergs
Berger, Sylvia 94 Eternal Light
308:9 Personal Story
353:8 Studio One
Berk, Howard 260:1 NBC Matinee Theater
264:3
Berkmans Ted 413:1 United States Steel Hour
Bernstein, Leonard 277 New York Philharmonic Young People's Concerts
Berrigan, Daniel 59 Catholic Hour
Berry, Duane H. 430:15 You Are There
Bethencourt, Francis 209:19 Lux Video Theater
Bigelow, Joe 155 Johnny Carson Show
239 Music on Ice
325 Red Skelton
Bimonte, Richard 386:6 United States Steel Hour
Black, Walter 243:15 My Son, Jeep
381 True Story
Blacker, Irwin 278 Odyssey
Bloch, John W. 88 Directions
207 Look Up and Live
Bloom, Philip 373:8 Suspense Theater
Bloomgraden, Lee 63:1 Center Stage
Blum, Edwin 213:8 Lux Video Theater
Blumgarten, James 89:9 Dumont Television Network
370:8 Studio One
378:11 Tales of Tomorrow
Bode, William T. 364:4 Studio One
Bodeen, DeWitt 65:9 Climax!
66:2
66:4
66:5
67:1
Bogart, Vincent 106 The Garry Moore Show
Boretz, Alvin 4:4 Alcoa Hour
5:4
7:6
14:1 Armstrong Circle Theater
15:7
17:5
18:3
18:8
20:5
21:2
21:4
22:1
22:5
23:2
23:5
25:7
27:2
42 Big Story
166 Justice
262:8 NBC Matinee Theater
266:1
266:9
Borisoff, Norman 37 Big Story
Bourjailly, Vance 15:4 Armstrong Circle Theater
16:4
17:1
18:6
255:3 NBC Matinee Theater
314:1 Philco Television Playhouse
Bowers, William 121:23 General Electric Theater
154 Jane Wyman Fireside Theater
Bower, Wilson 9:10 Armstrong Circle Theater
Brady, Leo 59 The Catholic Hour
88 Directions
207:20 Look Up and Live
364:1 Studio One
Brandel, Marc 68:3 Climax!
100:6 Front Row Center
102:1
190:4 Kraft Television Theater
254:3 NBC Matinee Theater
312:6 Philco Television Playhouse
358:2 Studio One
362:1
365:5
367:1
369:2
378:13 Television Playhouse
Brandfield, Jerome 210:8 Lux Video Theater
Brandstaetter, Roman 196 Lamp Unto My Feet
Braus, Mortimer 216:5 Lux Video Theater
Brenner, Alfred 6:8 Appointment With Adventure
13:2 Armstrong Circle Theater
82:10 Danger
166 Justice
257:9 NBC Matinee Theater
392:3 United States Steel Hour
394:6
400:3
Breen, Edward 390:6 United States Steel Hour
Brewer, Jameson 121:16 General Electric Theater
439:1 Drama Special
Bridges, Ann Preston 318:4 Pond's Theater
Brock, Jonathan 154 Jamie
Brodney, Oscar 121:17 General Electric Theater
Brook, Peter 279:6 Omnibus
Brooke, Rupert 341:3 Star Tonight
Brooks, Jack 122 George Gobel Show
Brooks, Mel 46 Caesar's Hour
Brooks, Norman 394:1 United States Steel Hour
Brown, Billings 373:8 Suspense Theater
Brown, Michael 5:3 Alcoa Hour
Brown, Stanley G. 162:8 Johnson's Wax
Brown, Walter C. 383:2 United States Steel Hour
Bruce, George 69:1 Climax!
Buck, Pearl 4:3 Alcoa Hour
163:6 Johnson's Wax Theater
Buckner, Robert 98:2 Ford Star Jubilee
98:3
Bullock, Harvey 335:6 Saturday Color Carnival
Bullock, Turner 58:12 Campbell Soundstage
388:4 United States Steel Hour
388:8
Bundt, Ellie 103 Frontiers of Faith
Burdett, Winston 381 The Twentieth Century
Burke, Robert David 8:8 Appointment with Adventure
Burns, Stan 343 Steve Allen Show
Burt, Frank 121:17 General Electric Theater
Burton, Jay 1:10 Accent On Comedy
35 The Big Party
166 Julius LaRosa Show
173 Kraft Music Hall
290 Perry Como Show
296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
318 Pontiac Star Parade
435 Entertainment Special
Burwell, Basil 83:8 Danger
Cagle, Charles 259:4 NBC Matinee Theater
Caillou, Alan 404:6 United States Steel Hour
Caiden, Martin 442 Documentary Special
Calabrese, Don 372:3 Studio One
Callahan, Stephen R. 253:4 NBC Matinee Theater
Callen, Harold 142:5 Hallmark Hall of Fame
142:9
143:9
144:2
145:1
147:1
147:2
246:9 NBC Matinee Theater
247:8
256:7
Calvelli, Joseph 205 The Lineup
233 The Mighty O
Calvey, Peter 417 The Web
Cameron, Kenneth 207 Look Up and Live
Camus, Albert 206 Look Up and Live
(Canfield, Dorothy) 400:4 United States Steel Hour
Capa, Albert 83:4 Danger
Carland, Richard 157:5 Johnson's Wax Theater
Carlson, Richard 192:7 Kraft Television Theater
Carlton, Sam 127 George Jessell Show
Carpenter, Joel 340:2 Star Stage
340:4
Carrington, Elaine 161:4 Johnson's Wax Theater
Carroll, Carroll 43 Bob Crosby
97:17 Ford Star Jubilee
155 Johnny Carson
Carroll, Sidney 3:7 Alcoa Hour
405:8 United States Steel Hour
406:1
408:1
408:7
410:7
412:3
437:4 Drama Special
Carson, Johnny 155 Johnny Carson Show
Carson, Robert 180:6 Kraft Television Theater
Carter, Samuel 227 Medical Horizons
Case, Theodore W. 9:12 Armstrong Circle Theater
Casey, Arden 364:8 Studio One
Casey, Rosemary 330:1 Richard Hudnut Theater
Cavanagh, Arthur 175:6 Kraft Television Theater
177:5
245:7 NBC Matinee Theater
Cavanagh, James 66:3 Climax!
67:4
68:7
69:5
73:3
85:8 Danger
100:4 Front Row Center
370:5 Studio One
370:6
373:3 Suspense Theater
373:12
374:2
374:6
374:12
375:2
375:4
375:10
375:11
375:12
375:17
376:2
Chain, Barbara 403:1 United States Steel Hour
Chamberlin, Mary 342:14 Star Tonight
Chandler, David 375 NBC Matinee Theater
Chandler, Raymond 372:5 Studio One
Chapin, Anne 72:5 Climax!
Chayefsky, Paddy 129:3 Goodyear Televison Plahouse
129:7
130:1
132:7
138:16 Gulf Playhouse
309:9 Philco Television Playhouse
310:6
31l:5
312:3
Chermiak, Cy 101:4 Front Row Center
Chodorov, Stephan 196 Lamp Unto My Feet
207 Look Up and Live
439:4 Drama Special
Christopherson, Glenna 414:6 United States Steel Hour
Citron, Samuel J. 207 Look Up and Live
Claborne, Robert 251:6 NBC Matinee Theater
Claiborne, Ross 276:3 NBC Matinee Theater
Claman, Julian 7:3 Appointment with Adventure
Clare, John 375:6 Suspense Theater
Clark, Dennis 86 Directions
Clark, Don 433:7 You Are There
433:9
Clarke, William Kendall 162:6 Johnson's Wax Theater
163:5
336:7 Schick Theater
337:3
382:8 United States Steel Hour
Claudel, Paul 208 Look Up and Live
Clauss, H.N. 400:1 United States Steel Hour
Clement, Joe 207 Look Up and Live
Cobb, Peter W. 9:1 Armstrong Circle Theater
Cochran, Joseph 188 Kraft Television Theater
212:8 Lux Video Theater
238:3 Motorola Televison Hour
Cockrell, Francis 122:2 General Electric Theater
377:3 Suspicion
377:9
Cockrell, Marion 122:2 General Electric Theater
377:8 Suspicion
Cohen, Larry 173:8 Kraft Mystery Theater
408:3 United States Steel Hour
Collier, John 1:3 ABC Album
Collins, Hal 147 Honestly, Celeste!
Collins, Richard 154 Jane Wyman Fireside Theater
Conebeare, Arthur Rodney 246:10 NBC Matinee Theater
372:4 Studio One
Conkle, E.P. 121:7 General Electric Theater
Connelly, Marc 145:11 Hallmark Hall of Fame
Cook, Joe 307 Perry Presents
Cook, Whitfield 69:2 Climax!
73:4
77:10
98:7 Front Row Center
99:3
100:1
197 Life with Father
431:14 You Are There
431:15
438 Drama Special
Cooke, Alan 37 Big Story
Cooper, Dorothy 321 Professional Father
Cooper, Felix 89:7 Dumont Television Network
Cooper, Irving H. 393:6 United States Steel Hour
Cooper, Mae 387:7 United States Steel Hour
Cooper, Wyllis 351:2 Studio One
Coopersmith, Jerome 6:14 Appointment with Adventure
11:10 Armstrong Circle Theater
12:5
13:4
13:7
13:12
14:4
16:1
19:7
21:1
22:8
24:2
24:4
26:8
27:5
42 Big Story
134:3 Goodyear Television Theater
155 Johnny Jupiter
173:11 Kraft Mystery Theater
409:4 United States Steel Hour
Copp, DeWitt 187:8 Kraft Televison Theater
Corcoran, Bob 92 Ellery Queen
Corfman, Eunice Luccock 258:1 NBC Matinee Theater
Costigan, James 121:11 General Electric Theater
174:3 Kraft Television Theater
225:4 Maurice Evans Presents
388:3 United States Steel Hour
390:2
418 The Web
Cotterell, Geoffrey 381:4 The TV Hour
Cotton, Helen 178:4 Kraft Television THeater
279:2 NBC Matinee Theater
362:5 Studio One
368:1
388:5 United States Steel Hour
391:6
401:3
Coughlan, Robert 281:5 Omnibus
Cousin, Michele 245:3 NBC Matinee
343:6 Star Tonight
441:7 Drama Special
Cousins, Margaret 65:2 Climax
439:12 Drama Special
Coward, Noel 98:1 Ford Star Jubilee
Cowley, William 240 My Favorite Husband
Coxe, George Harmon 191:5 Kraft Television Theater
Crabtree, Paul 183:3 Kraft Television Theater
184:1
362:9 Studio One
365:2
365:4
Cramoy, Michael 82:11 Danger
321 Professional Father
Crane, Chet 78 Colonel Humphrey Flack
Crane, Harry 151 Jackie Gleason Show
Craven, Frank 261:6 NBC Matinee Theater
Crawford, Oliver 72:1 Climax!
72:7
75:9
186:7 Kraft Television Theater
195:2
220:5 Lux Video Theater
Crean, Robert 25:5 Armstrong Circle Theater
26:2
27:3
60 Catholic Hour
88 Directions
189:3 Kraft Television Theater
189:4
195:5
196 Lamp Unto My Feet
409:7 United States Steel Hour
413:2
Crilly, John 237:1 Motorola Television Hour
Crocker, Emerson 351:3 Studio One
352:1
Croswell, Anne 397:5 United States Steel Hour
Crutcher, Robert Riley 240 My Favorite Husband
Crutchfield, Les 139 Gunsmoke
Cunningham, Joan 7:7 Appointment with Adventure
7:9
8:2
166 Justice
Curtis, Nathaniel 158:3 Johnson's Wax Theater
Cutler, Stan 264:6 NBC Matinee Theater
Dahl, Roald 314:8 Philip Morris Playhouse
Dana, Bill 343 Steve Allen Show
Daniel, Jeremy 80:12 Danger
85:9
85:10
427:7 You Are There
427:12
427:14
428:5
428:7
428:10
428:16
429:3
429:4
429:6
430:3
430:4
430:8
430:16
430:17
431:3
431:4
Daniels, Norman 417 The Web
Dann, Sam 92 Ellery Queen
190:1 Kraft Television Theater
David, Paul 283 On Trial
David, S.L. 78 Colonel Humphrey Flack
Davidson, Barbara Kay 253:3 NBC Matinee Theater
260:2
Davidson, David 2:9 Alcoa Hour
3:3
18:2 Armstrong Cirlce Theater
24:6
58:11 Campbell Soundstage
91:4 Elgin Hour
187:7 Kraft Television Theater
189:6
227:12 Medallion Theater
236:6 Moment of Fear
236:8
237:2 Motorola Television Hour
237:7
238:2
266:10 NBC Matinee Theater
316:5 Playwrights '56
361:7 Studio One
381:10 United States Steel Hour
383:3
393:5
400:5
443:9 Documentary Special
Davis, Dorothy Salisbury 388:7 United States Steel Hour
Davis, Howard Lawrence 260:4 NBC Matinee Theater
Davis, Leo 121:3 General Electric Theater
121:4
430:13 You Are There
431:7
Dayton, Elderous L. 445:4 Documentary Special
DeBlasio, Edward 182:2 Kraft Television Theater
DeBono 171:4 Kaiser Aluminum Hour
DeFelitta, Frank P. 2 Adventure
57:7 Campbell Soundstage
57:10
57:16
57:17
58:5
83:10 Danger
84:4
84:8
226:13 Medallion Theater
278 Odyssey
375:14 Suspense Theater
376:8
376:9
426:5 Windows
443:1 Documentary Special
DeGaszto, Carmen 207 Look Up and Live
Delph, Dagny 160:8 Johnson's Wax Theater
Denham, Reginald 237:4 Motorola Television Theater
Denker, Henry 190:3 Kraft Television Theater
401:5 United States Steel Hour
DeRoy, Richard 340:14 Star Stage
364:4 Studio One
369:6
371:9
Deutsch, Helen 320:5 Producer's Showcase
De Vries, John 341:7 Star Tonight
Diamond, Mel 151 Jackie Gleason
Diamond, Selma 35 The Big Party
46 Caesar Presents
46 Caesar's Hour
173 Kraft Music Hall
285 Pat Boone Chevy Showroom
296 Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall
(Dickens, Charles) 159:7 Johnson's Wax Theater
334:1 Robert Montgomery Presents
Disney, Dorothy Miles 17 Kraft Mystery Theater
Dolinsky, Meyer 246:8 NBC Matinee Theater
Doniger, Walter 437 Drama Special
Donner, Robert 86 Directions
Donovan, Martin 260:9 NBC Matinee Theater
Dortort, David 199 Lineup
Douglas, Jack 122 George Gobel Show
Dowel, Mary 80:15 Danger
(Doyle, Arthur Conan) 373:9 Suspense Theater
Drew, Bernard 210:5 Lux Video Theater
240 My Favorite Husband
Dreyfus, Michael 5:3 Alcoa Hour
Driscoll, David 5:2 Alcoa Hour
Duffield, Brainard 99:6 Front Row Center
99:7
197 Life With Father
371:2 Studio One
Duffy, Lucile 392:4 United States Steel Hour
DuMaurier, Daphne 373:3 Suspense Theater
Duncan, Leslie 181:1 Kraft Television Theater
392:2 United States Steel Hour
Duncan, Bob and Wanda 270:2 NBC Matinee Theater
273:7
392:6 United States Steel Hour
396:3
Dunham, Stuart 256:2 NBC Matinee Theater
Dunkel, John 139 Gunsmoke
Dunning, Philip 34:7 Best of Broadway
Durkee, Dorcas 10:10 Armstrong Circle Theater
Durkee, F.W. 68:6 Climax!
312:1 Philco Television Playhouse
313:1
316:4 Playwrights '56
Dyne, Michael 5:9 Alcoa Hour
12:10 Armstrong Circle Theater
17:2
90:10 Elgin Hour
91:7
104 Further Adventures of Ellery Queen
183:6 Kraft Television Theater
195:1
247:4 NBC Matinee Theater
251:1
261:7
268:10
353:9 Studio One
356:9
357:2
358:1
360:1 Studio One
360:6
362:8
371:1
373:1 Suspense Theater
373:9
373:10
374:8
374:10
375:15
376:7
383:5 United States Steel Hour
402:1
411:3
412:6
Dyslin, George E. 189:2 Kraft Television Theater
Ebin, David 86 Directions
196 Lamp Unto My Feet
207 Look Up and Live
278 Odyssey
Eckhardt, Agnes 157:7 Johnson's Wax Program
157:10
165:4
333:2 Robert Montgomery Presents
333:6
Edge, Fred 188:3 Kraft Television Theater
Edwards, Blake 199 Lineup
Eggers, Fred 199 Lineup
233 The Mighty O
Ehrlich, Max 23:1 Armstrong Circle Theater
37 Big Story
223 The Mail Story
368:2 Studio One
368:3
Elkin, Samuel 12:1 Armstrong Circle Theater
193:1 Kraft Television Theater
207:11 Look Up and Live
Elkram, William 99:1 Front Row Center
Elliott, Sumner Locke 5:1 Alcoa Hour
129:2 Goodyear Television Playhouse
130:2
130:6
132:5
172:1 Kaiser Aluminum Hour
309:7 Philco Television Playhouse
311:6
312:4
315:6 Playwrights '56
315:9
316:7
319:1 Producerts Showcase
319:6
365:6 Studio One
379:9 Theater 62
402:6 United States Steel Hour
439:10 Drama Special
Ellis, Anthony 65:3 Climax!
Elman, Irving 11:9 Armstrong Circle Theater
12:6
66:7 Climax!
Elward, James 194:3 Kraft Television Theater
196 Lamp Unto My Feet
207 Look Up and Live
254:1 NBC Matinee Theater
396:2 United States Steel Hour
397:1
Emmett, Robert 179:3 Kraft Television Theater
269:5 NBC Matinee Theater
317:6 Pond's Theater
386:7 United States Steel Hour
393:2
398:4
Emmons, Charles L. 209:20 Lux Video Theater
Engel, Leonard 45 Breakthrough
Epstein, Herman J. 263:9 NBC Matinee Theater
Esson, Robert 85:11 Danger
247:5 NBC Matinee Theater
247:9
252:9
255:10
259:11
262:2
264:2
265:12
267:1
267:11
271:10
272:1
274:2
274:5
275:7
276:1
Ettlinger, Don 104 Further Adventures of Ellery Queen
154 Jamie
185:9 Kraft Television Theater
358:9 Studio One
361:3
Ettlinger, Katrina 185:9 Kraft Television Theater
Eunson, Katherine and Dale 215:5 Lux Video Theater
Fairservis, Walter 2 Adventure
278 Odyssey
Falk-Ronne, Hans Peter 332:2 Robert Montgomery Presents
Farr, Finis 8:15 Appointment with Adventure
Fass, George and Gertrude 81:8 Danger
Fast, Howard 94 The Eternal Light
Faulkner, George H. 10:5 Armstrong Circle Theater
176:6 Kraft Television Theater
193:3
383:8 United States Steel Hour